[Music]
so uh myself so tan I'm vice president
for health agency so we take care of
Health product so recently we talked
about uh the Elevate product that we
have launched so there are the four
major features about the product that I
will again brief you so infinite care
was one where in a customer can take an
x amount of UN number of amount of claim
in his once once in his lifetime then
was a power booster where can where in
his policy actually uh gets doubled
every year so if he buys a 10 lakh
policy it becomes 20 lakhs the next year
this is again an add-on cover next 10
years a 10 lak policy will become a 1 CR
policy and so on and so forth right
third was the jump start that we talked
about where in a customer if he has a
ped so he can get the cover from 31st
day as in the normal policy if you see
to it PD has different different uh
somebody covers it in two years some
covers it in 3 years with jump start it
it gets covered in 31st day only then
there was a unlimited some insured uh uh
add-on feature that we had where a
customer can buy unlimited some insured
policy so these are the major features
that we have in our product apart from
these features we have some 18 add-on
covers that that a customer can buy
depending upon his needs so we had b in
a modular chasc product right wherein if
a customer needs some of the other ad on
he can pick and choose and he can uh pay
the premium and get his policy done so
now it's totally dependent on the
customer see again this product is again
based on AI that we talked about so
we'll actually give customer an added
Advantage we'll recommend him a plan
this is the best suited plan for that
particular customer so if depending upon
the demography depending upon his family
size depending upon what age he's into
right depending upon his income
everything so we'll curate a plan for
him and we will recommend a plan to that
customer so these are the major features
that we have launched in this product
what is the main reason to launch thison
to launch this so the main reason is
that we want to see again if you see
today India as a country we are only we
have only 5% penetration in health
insurance space so we want to grow we
are already number one in other segments
we want to be number one inth space as
well what's the person market share what
the fut so q1 if I talk about uh is 2.9%
market share in health space and overall
health this is retail health I'm talking
about 2.9% and overall health space if
we see uh taking into corent a group
business as well so we are at
11.4% and see we as an organization want
to be at the
top thec
sorry policy see uh that is called a
jump start feature where in there are
five lifestyle diseases so there is
asema there is obesity hypertension
hyper lipidemia so all these diseases
are taking into go these are called
lifestyle diseases so if a customer opts
for that jump start addon cover he
starts getting his ped covered
pre-existing disease covered from the
31st day if he doesn't take that cover
it is a 3E waiting period in the PED if
it takes that cover it comes down to 31
basically this this this is all the dis
including cancer no only five lifestyle
diseases obesity hypertension hyper
lipidemia asema